<Events>

    <Blacksmith>
        <Value Value="1">
            <Text RewardMessage="Blacksmith Unlocked">A wandering blacksmith has found her way into town, apparently guided by one of the adventurers that left a while back. She set up shop in one of the houses, and you can buy weapons and armour from her.</Text>
        </Value>
        <Value Value="2">
            <Text RewardMessage="Blacksmith Upgraded">The discovery of a site for mining iron has allowed to blacksmith to forge new equipment.</Text>
        </Value>
        <Value Value="3">
            <Text RewardMessage="Blacksmith Upgraded">The discovery of a site for mining coal has allowed to blacksmith to smelt steel and forge new equipment.</Text>
        </Value>
        <Value Value="4">
            <Text RewardMessage="Blacksmith Upgraded">The discovery of a site for mining starion has allowed to blacksmith to forge new equipment.</Text>
        </Value>
        <Value Value="5">
            <Text RewardMessage="Blacksmith Upgraded">The discovery of a site for mining ferrusite has allowed to blacksmith to forge new equipment.</Text>
        </Value>
        <Value Value="6">
            <Text RewardMessage="Blacksmith Upgraded">The discovery of a site for mining silverium has allowed to blacksmith to forge new equipment.</Text>
        </Value>
    </Blacksmith>

    <Mage>
        <Value Value="1">
            <Text RewardMessage="Mage Class Unlocked">A group of mages and their apprentices have arrived in the village, and set up a small magic school. The apprentices can head out on adventures to gain experience if they desire.</Text>
        </Value>
    </Mage>

    <Fighter>
        <Value Value="1">
            <Text RewardMessage="Fighter Class Unlocked">A group of soldiers and their squires have arrived in the village, and set up a small training camp. The soldiers can head out on adventures to gain experience and funds if they desire.</Text>
        </Value>
    </Fighter>

    <Hunter>
        <Value Value="1">
            <Text RewardMessage="Hunter Class Unlocked">A group of hunters and their trainees have arrived in the village, and set up a small archery range. The hunters can head out on hunts to gain experience if they desire.</Text>
        </Value>
    </Hunter>

    <MerchantHelped>
        <Value>
            <Text RewardMessage="Starting Funds Increased">A merchant arrived in town, reporting his survival to be thanks to an adventurer from the village. He's agreed to set up a trade route with the town, increasing our funds.</Text>
            <AddFunds>10</AddFunds>
        </Value>
    </MerchantHelped>

    <VillagersFreed>
        <Value>
            <Text RewardMessage="Starting Funds Increased">Some of the captured villagers stumble back into town, telling stories of the mighty adventurer who saved them from the goblin clutches.</Text>
            <AddFunds>5</AddFunds>
        </Value>
    </VillagersFreed>

</Events>